(door slams)
(sighs)
(Howard:)Raj, wait.
(Raj:)What took you so long?
LEONARD:
Buddy, I know me
(Sheldon:)moving in with Penny
feels like a big change,
(Leonard:)but it's not.
(Sheldon:)How can you say that?
(Sheldon:)Amy's gone,
(Sheldon:)and you two are married now,
(Sheldon:)so it's only a matter of time
before you're gone, too.
(Penny:)Okay, you don't know
what's gonna happen.
(Sheldon:)No, I do.
(Sheldon:)Eventually you'll want
more space,
(Sheldon:)and you'll move into a house,
(Sheldon:)and then instead of dinner
a couple of times a week,
(Sheldon:)it'll only be a couple
of times a month,
(Sheldon:)and then it'll only be
(Sheldon:)on special occasions,
(Sheldon:)like when Bernadette
divorces Wolowitz.
Or-or-or like
(Sheldon:)when Koothrappali's
weird girlfriend
(Sheldon:)admits where she buried
his body.
(Sheldon:)Or Amy's wedding,
(Sheldon:)where she's marrying
someone better than me.
(Penny:)Okay, look,
(Penny:)we don't need
to rush into anything.
(Penny:)All right?
(Penny:)Maybe instead of Leonard
moving in with me,